This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After losing his brother Ace during the War of the Best, Luffy was distraught.
Me! King of the Pirates!
He was soon surprised by Dark King Rayleigh's unexpected appearance at the Maiden Island.
I may have another suggestion for you.
After they learned of Ace's death at Marineford,
the rest of the Straw Hats made haste to reunite with Luffy and offer their support.
Encounter! The Great Swordsman Mihawk! Zoro's self-will deadly struggle!
The Great SwordsmanOlive
This is Gloom Island on the Grand Line.
Home to the ruins of the Monkey Kingdom.
An old castle remains from the long-dead empire.
Despite its age, a well-known figure has made the castle his home.
Why did Mario have to get himself killed?
You're being a pest.
Go and cry somewhere else.
How can you be so heartless when I'm grieving?
Show some compassion, you big meanie!
Do you have anything kind to say?
Offer me a tissue!
I'm your guest!
Your manners are appalling!
I never invited you.
The two of you showed up and started living here without asking.
Furthermore, this article is not credible.
What?
But does that mean Moriya could still be alive?
He made it out?
A good question, now you ask.
If he died, then I didn't see it.
Although, if he did escape, then I didn't see that either, I'm afraid.
But you think he might have survived and they're lying about it for some reason?
Perhaps.
Huh?
What are you doing out of bed?
You're hurt!
Bad!
Are you crazy?!
Put those swords down, you moron!
Don't tell me you're gonna try and fight them again!
Give up!
You're lucky you survived the first fight!
Those baboons will murder you!
Shut up!
Keep your nose out of my business!
Got it?!
How could you say such a cruel thing to me?!
I dragged your stupid body all the way back here!
Without my help, you'd beat Monkey Chow!
Hawkeye...
Give it a rest already!
You can barely even walk!
You're wounded.
Stay here.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Have you forgotten?
You told me what happened to my captain!
I have to go!
He should still be alive, but unfortunately he appears to be severely traumatized.
Firefist Ace died.
Right before Straw Hat's eyes.
All this time...
And I never even knew the war was happening.
But Luffy's alright!
Are you sure?
Where is he now?!
Can't you tell me anything else?!
No, alas.
That's all I know.
Fine.
Then I'll leave you alone.
Hey, stupid!
Hold on!
You're never gonna make it to the shore without those baboon things attacking you!
And even if you do get there, how are you gonna cross the sea?!
If you want a boat, circle around the castle, west side.
Thank you for that.
Are you kidding me?!
Dummy!
That's the last time I saved you a grateful butt!
You can bury your own corpse when they kill you!
Luffy, although you just lost your brother, no matter what, I know that you'll still keep your promise.
That's why I'll get back to Saba Odi too.
At any cost!
It's about time.
I knew you guys weren't gonna let me go that easily.
That's my full demon technique!
And that's the Dragon Twister!
They've learned to copy my three-sword style!
Hey, Shelps!
Copying me?
Pathetic!
How can you be satisfied with yourselves?
You aren't real swordsmen?!
Damn it!
You can't mess with me like that!
After all I've done for him, he doesn't appreciate anything!
I hope he drops dead.
Yeah, that'd serve him right and I wouldn't care one bit!
If you're that worried about Roronoa, go AFRARA mailing
If you're that worried about RORO NOAA!
Go L saved you guys, find me.
That's a natural man!
Is he okay if you'd come back?
Oh, uh, go look for him.
You think I'm worried about him?
What gave you that impression, huh?
In any case, I don't think he'll die so easily.
Yeah? You're wrong.
By the time Kuma got to him, he was already banged up,
and since he showed up at the castle, he's only gotten worse.
And those baboons don't exactly strike me as the merciful type.
Damn, damn, damn! This isn't fair!
If Zoro gets himself killed out there, I'll be stuck with Hawkeye.
And he's downright rude to my stuffed animals.
And as a host, he hasn't offered me hot cocoa, not even one time!
You may be kind of an oaf, Zoro,
but you're still a lot more fun to have around than that old dirtbag!
So don't get killed out there, okay?
3,000 worlds!
But why?
Scars on the back.
Or swordsman's shame.
Fine.
Yuh-hoo! Zoro!
Are you still alive?
I haven't spotted a single sign of him all day.
But he couldn't have set sail!
No.
No, don't tell me he got lost again.
Honey?
Giddy!
You can't fix that with your spits!
Who even taught you that garbage, your grandma?
Bastards!
They may be stupid, but damn, they're strong.
At this rate, I'm never going to make it to the sea.
Hawkeye.
It's been quite a while since you left the castle,
yet you've only made it this far.
Pity.
And the boat I offered you,
it seems it's not seaworthy now.
Shut up!
It's fine!
We can just hold on to a few planks and swim there.
I'm not one to give up that easily, alright?
Your sentiment is admirable,
but you can't defeat them.
They're called humandrils,
baboons that develop by imitating human behavior.
Humandrils?
Had they grown up among peace-loving humans,
they would have turned out differently.
But not on this island.
Up until seven years ago,
this was the site of a great war.
When I first came here to live,
the entire island still smelled of blood and smoke.
Everywhere, dead bodies littered the ground.
As the battles raged on,
these baboons watched the violence between the humans unfold.
In time, they learned how to use human weapons and armor,
becoming warriors of the forest.
Humans can defeat ordinary animals by using weapons and intellect.
But what happens when animals don weapons as well?
As you can see,
they make formidable opponents for an arrogant young man.
You talking about me?
Well, who else?
Now, let's leave.
It's late.
The humandrils won't set foot near the castle.
Yeah?
You got no right telling me what to do.
I've got to make it to the sea.
Of course.
Do as you like.
I don't care if they're forest warriors or monkeys.
I've already wasted enough time stranded in this dump.
I'm cutting down every single one of them.
Come on.
That doof's got to be around here somewhere.
There.
But the baboon's got to it first.
Zoro, no!
No!
Meanwhile, in the land of Hungaria, on Lazy Bones Island...
What is he doing?
He's been in that shack forever.
If Lord Satan's going to help us curse the Longarm Tribe,
then how come it's so quiet?
Lord Satan knows what he's doing.
There's no doubt in my mind that our Savior is bringing forth a powerful incantation
to deal the tyrannical Longarm Tribe a fatal blow.
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Greetings, everyone.
Thank you for waiting.
Is the ritual finally over?
Atta boy, Satan!
My work is now complete.
I hope it will do the trick.
What is he holding?
And here you go.
Oh, thank you, Lord.
What is it?
Just a little ditty.
Wait, no!
Don't tell me!
Huh?
Our prayers have finally been answered.
Satan has pinned a set of talismans to help us kill the Longarm Tribe.
Lord Satan has doomed the Longarms to an agonizing death.
Huh?
We're now as good as invincible.
Try as they might, even those Longarm bullies can't lay their hands on us anymore.
I bet the mere sight of these symbols will strike them dead.
Not exactly.
How awesome!
That's Lord Satan for you.
Come on, men!
Everybody grab a page and find a place to nail it up around town!
Be quick!
No, it's not like that.
You really shouldn't separate them!
Oh.
Oh, goodness!
Hello!
They're all posted now.
Yes.
Excellent work, friends.
I finally feel safe now.
We all owe you our lives.
Thank you, Lord.
Uh...
Sir!
We have a problem!
The Longarm Tribe is on their way here!
Those simpletons are like moths to a flame.
Now we sit back and watch, for as of today, our enemies are history!
Hold on!
Um, that thing with all the pages?
It's actually a musical score, not a talisman at all.
Huh?
What?
Well, we're dead.
They'll take our food.
What few things of value we have, they'll claim as their own.
People will be kidnapped.
Life will be miserable.
We have no choice.
You always have a choice.
Lord Satan.
Please, lend me your ears, if you would.
This song?
What's it doing?
It's as if my body is filling with a brand new energy!
What the hell is this?
Some kind of spell?
Not only do people with one joint in their arm look funny, but they think funny, too.
What are they up to this time?
Huh?
Well now, what's this?
From this day forth, we no longer allow the Long-Arm Tribe to terrorize our people.
Huh?
That's right!
We're finally fighting back!
Yeah!
You're not taking anything else from us!
We're gonna protect that which is ours with our own hands!
Make your move!
We're not afraid of you!
Now you've got it!
Hey, boss, they're acting kind of different than usual.
All right.
Guess we need to remind these short-arms we own them!
Attack!
Let's go!
You're truly a blessing from hell.
Thank you, Lord Satan.
It's unreal.
I never imagined that one day we'd be able to fight back like that, much less beat them
and put them in a cage.
The music!
Something about it changed us!
I've never felt so uplifted before!
He's right!
Courage and strength welled up in our hearts!
We stood up and defended ourselves for the first time in our lives!
Hmm.
Of course we had no idea how to use our weapons.
Ultimately, you did most of the actual fighting by yourself.
But that's okay.
What matters is the people who were abducted came back safely.
No, you're too modest.
I only helped a teeny bit.
Neither gods nor devils will help those who won't fight on their own.
In times like these, it is important to stand resolute against evil,
even if the odds seem insurmountable.
You have the courage.
You prove that today.
Such a wise god!
You've inspired us!
We'll do our best to make you proud!
Thank you very much for your teaching!
Hail, Lord, Satan!
I hope that repaid their kindness.
Still, I can't believe the news.
Please stay strong, Luffy.
I hope you're alright.
I'll be there soon to share in your grief.
If I had a heart, it would be heavy.
Until I can return to your side,
all I can do is play a song and hope that it reaches you somehow.
Damn it!
I can't believe they got the devil as their bodyguard.
What an embarrassment!
They should be the ones in cages with those freakish single-jointed arms of theirs on display.
Actually, we could make a lot of money doing that, couldn't we?
Good idea.
Huh?
We'll put their freakish double-jointed arms on display.
They owe us, and we can certainly make a lot of money doing that.
Wait just a minute!
That's wrong!
Huh?
And it's immoral!
I'm certain that you didn't appreciate it when they were cruel to you.
Huh?
Everyone, listen to me.
Let them go?
How could we, Lord Satan?
They'll just come back and attack us again.
No, they will not.
I'll make sure of that by binding them to a devil's contract.
Heed my words well.
If you break your oath with me and commit a wrongful act against the people in this country
again, I will hunt each of you down.
And then I will eat your heart!
Thank you, sir.
We promise you will behave.
We're going straight back to our homes.
We'll never come back again.
No, please don't hurt us.
You three are free to go, but you must always remember, do not treat others poorly.
If somebody went into your country causing havoc and destruction, then I'm sure you'd be
unhappy.
It doesn't matter if you have one or two joints in your arms.
Deep down, we're all the same.
So treat each other with respect.
Yes, thank you!
Now grab him!
What's the big idea here?
Away we go!
Sorry, but we don't believe in curses.
Also, your speech was stupid and you fell for the oldest trick in the book.
If we bring back an actual walking, talking skeleton...
We can make a whole ton of money!
Wait a minute!
Let me go!
I have somewhere I need to be!
Oh no.
We have an emergency!
Lord Satan has just been kidnapped!
Everyone, prepare to summon another devil!
And fast!
Yes!
We can still summon devils with the magical power of underwear!
Luffy, when you feel sad, just sing a song.
Music is meant to make you happy.
So sing as you wait for me.
I'll try to.
No, I will be there.
Until then, if you can hear me...
Sandra, help!
Well then, that's it.
I'm sorry.
What did you just say to him?
You heard.
You were right here the whole time.
No!
I'm finding it difficult to understand your intentions.
Surely you know what's going on in Luffy's mind right now.
Think of all he's been through!
Depending on your answer, I may not be able to forgive you!
I agree.
How dare you suggest such a thing!
And so soon after the war!
It's simply cruel!
I made a suggestion, that's all.
Only Luffy can decide.
So what's your decision?
I don't know.
All my friends...
I never want them to go through something like that again.
If I do like you tell me to, will it help me protect them?
No promises, but it's certainly worth a shot.
That said, you do realize you have a lot of work to do.
Okay.
I've made up my mind.
If you think I should, I'll go back.
To Marineford!
After learning of Ace's death, Sanji plots to return to Saba-Ori.
However, his plans are thwarted when Ivankov makes his long-awaited return to the Kamabaka kingdom.
Burning with determination, Sanji begins a fierce battle with his pride on the line.
On the next, One Piece, a disaster for Sanji, the Queen's return to the kingdom.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!